<Mod
	name="SpicyTP:EUI"
	description="[h1]Spicy's Texture Pack: Elegant UI 1.3.2[/h1]
is a texture pack that gives Noita's UI a refined and shiny aesthetic.
[h3]Join the Discord![/h3]
[url=https://discord.gg/4nN8KHBY6R]My personal Discord[/url] contains categories for things that I work on. I'd recommend joining if you're interested in seeing early previews of what's being worked on.

[hr][/hr]
[h2]What sprites does this mod overhaul?[/h2]
This mod currently supports:
[list]
[*]Vanilla - [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/discussion/2887405712/4783413655229937398/]26 sprites[/url]
[/list]

[h3]See also[/h3]
To further customize your visuals, be sure to visit the [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2887423419]STP collection on the Steam Workshop[/url] or the [url=https://github.com/SpicySpaceSnake/SpicyTP/wiki]STP GitHub repository's wiki[/url].

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Is this mod compatible with X?[/h2]
This mod only overwrites image files and really shouldn't break anything.
At most, a Mod X that overrites the same files or edits the same sections of files as SpicyTP may take priority over this mod if Mod X loads after it; likewise, this mod will take priority over others, though that's beneficial at times due to the nature of this mod.
[b]To function correctly with SpicyTP:Core, this mod must be placed AFTER it in the load order.[/b]

Found a bug? Leave a comment or start a discussion!

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Will there ever be cross-mod support?[/h2]
[b]Maybe.[/b] Mods that add support-able UI elements aren't that common, and I'm not actively looking at the moment...
However, I'm not familiar with every mod out there. If you're the owner of (or somehow affiliated with) a mod that you want me to add support for, consider reaching out to ask!

[hr][/hr]
[h2]How often does this mod update?[/h2]
This mod is pretty much as done as it'll get. I may decide to edit or add sprites every so often, but there's not really any ETA on that.

[b]CURRENT FOCUS:[/b] none
[b]CURRENT STATUS:[/b] being passively maintained

[hr][/hr]
[h2]Credits go to[/h2]
[list]
[*][b]SpicySpaceSnake[/b] ([url=https://spicyspacesnake.carrd.co/]that's me![/url]): main artist
[*][b]Viowlet[/b] ([url=https://www.reddit.com/user/Viowlet/]u/Viowlet[/url]): their [url=https://www.reddit.com/r/noita/comments/jp56ub/a_while_ago_i_made_noita_blackletter_this_is_now]free-to-use Noita Blackletter font[/url]
[/list]
[h3]And a special thanks to[/h3]
[list]
[*][b]Siris[/b], for being a partial inspiration for the SpicyTP series
[*][b]Kirisis[/b], for being the light of my life and for her invaluable support and early feedback
[*][b]All of my partners[/b], for being a bunch of absolutely amazing people
[*][b]Copi, GrahamBurger, Conga Lyne, and many others[/b] that I've either worked with or gotten advice from, for their previous and continued support

[*]and [b]YOU[/b], for taking the time to check out this mod!
[/list]

Please be sure to rate on your way out, and share this with anyone you think might like it. Happy Noiting!"
	tags="graphics, quality of life"
	dont_upload_folders=""
	dont_upload_files="changelog.txt"
> 
</Mod>